This is Media Break.
You give us three minutes
and we'll give you the world.
Good morning.
I'm Casey Wong with Jesse Perkins.
Top story, Pretoria.
The threat of nuclear confrontation
in South Africa escalated today
when the ruling
white military government
of that besieged city-state
unveiled a French-made neutron bomb
and affirmed its willingness
to use the three megaton device
as the city's last line of defense.
And the President's
first press conference
from the Star Wars
orbiting peace platform
got off to a shaky start,
when power failed causing a brief,
but harmless,
period of weightlessness
for the visiting
President and his staff.
We'll be back in a moment.
Is it time for that big operation?
This may be the most
important decision of your life.
So come down and talk to one
of our qualified surgeons
here at the Family Heart Center.
We feature the complete Jarvik line,
series 7 Sports Heart by Jensen,
Yamaha.
You pick the heart.
Extended warranties, financing.
Qualifies for health tax credit.
And remember, we care.
Three dead police officers,
one critically injured.
Police union leaders blame
Omni Consumer Products, OCP,
the firm which recently entered
into a contract with the city
to fund and run the Detroit
Metropolitan Police Department.
Dick Jones,
Division President, OCP.
Every policeman knows
when he joins the force
that there are certain inherent risks
that come with the territory.
Ask any cop, he'll tell you,
"If you can't stand the heat,
you better stay out of the kitchen."
Although seriously wounded,
Officer Frank Frederickson escaped
and identified this man.
Clarence Boddicker,
unofficial crime boss of Old Detroit.
Now sought in connection with the
deaths of 31 police officers.
Today, he's at large,
while doctors at
Henry Ford Memorial Hospital
fight to save the life
of Officer Frank Frederickson.
Good luck, Frank.
Attempted murder?
It's not like he killed someone.
This is a clear violation
of my client's civil rights.
Make it aggravated assault,
and I can make bail, in cash, now.
Listen, pal, your client's a scumbag,
you're a scumbag,
and scumbags see the judge
on Monday morning!
Now get out of my police station,
and take laughing boy with you!
Get over there!
You have the right to remain
silent. Do you understand me?
Sure, sure.
- Priors?
- No.
Hi.
Uh, Murphy. Transferring in
from Metro South.
Nice precinct.
Yeah, pretty good.
We work for a living down here, Murphy.
Get your armor and suit up.
Please take me home!
Not now, E.J.
Get a cup of coffee.
Oh, Sarge.
Stark, is there any
word on Frederickson?
They're still listing
him as critical.
His wife must be going
out of her mind.
- Murphy, huh?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Manson.
- Hi.
What brings you to
this little paradise?
Beats me, man. I think OCP's moving
a lot of new guys up here.
Omni Consumer Products.
What a bunch of morons.
They're gonna manage this department
right into the ground!
- Where are you from?
- Metro South.
Welcome to hell.
- Murphy.
- Yo.
You cut 10 guys
loose over on the east side.
You try to get backup
when you're in a jam.
Yeah, try to get a medevac
after you've been jammed.
I'll tell you what we should do.
We should strike. Fuck 'em!
Oh, boy.
The funeral's tomorrow.
The department requests
all officers not on duty to attend.
Any donations for the family
may be given to Cecil as usual.
And I don't want to hear
any more talk about strike!
We're not plumbers.
We're police officers.
And police officers don't strike.
Murphy, front and center.
Hello, tiger.
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, yes!
Lewis, come here when you're finished
fucking around with your suspect.
Get on your feet!
This guy's gonna be
your new partner.
Murphy, meet Lewis.
Show him the neighborhood.
Glad to know you, Murphy.
Pretty neat.
I better drive until you
know your way around.
I usually drive when I'm
breaking in a new partner.
You really think
the old man is gonna be there?
Why would they invite us?
All division heads are
bringing their support teams.
It's big.
I figure they're green-lighting
Delta City.
What, are you kidding?
They never do anything ahead of schedule.
It's Jones. He's got the 209 series
online and now he wants to show off.
That's a tough break, Bob.
What? What?
Well, ED 209 ran into serious
delays and cost overruns.
The old man ordered a backup plan.
95th floor.
Have a nice day.
Probably just to
light a fire under Jones' ass.
- Yeah?
- Old Bob here gets the assignment.
Yeah.
Nobody in Security Concepts
takes it seriously.
It's a better plan. Fucking Jones! I'd
go straight to the Old Man if I could.
Don't mess with Jones, man.
He'll make sushi out of you.
Yeah, you better be careful, man.
I heard Jones is a real shark.
- Who asked you, twerp?
- Bob.
What about this police thing,
what's the problem?
Their union's been bitching
ever since we took over.
You know, the usual nonsense.
We'll turn things around.
Mmm-hmm. Good, very good.
Let's get started.
Now, friends,
I've had this dream
for more than a decade now.
A dream which I've invited you all
to share with me.
In six months, we begin construction
of Delta City.
Where Old Detroit now stands.
Old Detroit has a cancer.
The cancer is crime.
And it must be cut out before
we employ the 2 million workers
that will breathe life
into this city again.
Yes.
Although shifts in the tax structure
have created an economy
ideal for corporate growth,
community services,
in this case law enforcement,
have suffered.
I think it's time we
gave something back.
Dick.
Take a close look
at the track record of this company.
And you'll see that we have gambled
in markets
traditionally regarded as nonprofit.
Hospitals, prisons,
space exploration.
I say good business
is where you find it.
As you know, we've entered
into a contract with the city
to run local law enforcement.
But at Security Concepts,
we believe an efficient police force
is only part of the solution.
No. We need something more.
We need a 24-hour-a-day
police officer.
A cop that doesn't
need to eat or sleep.
A cop with superior firepower
and the reflexes to use it.
Fellow executives,
it gives me great pleasure to introduce
you to the future of law enforcement.
Ed 209.
The Enforcement Droid series 209 is a
self-sufficient law enforcement robot.
209 is currently programmed
for urban pacification,
but that is only the beginning.
After a successful tour of duty
in Old Detroit,
we can expect 209 to become the hot
military product for the next decade.
- Dr. McNamara.
- We'll need an arrest subject.
- Mr. Kinney.
- Yes, sir?
Would you come up
and give us a hand, please?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kinney is going to help us simulate
a typical arrest and disarming procedure.
Mr. Kinney, use your gun
in a threatening manner.
- Point it at Ed 209.
- Yes, sir.
Please put down your weapon.
You have 20 seconds to comply.
I think you'd better do what he says,
Mr. Kinney.
You now have 15 seconds to comply.
- You are in direct violation...
- Cut the power! Pull the board!
Of Penal Code 113, Section 9.
You now have five seconds to comply.
Help! Help me!
Four, three, two, one.
I am now authorized to
use physical force.
It's horrible.
Somebody want to call
a goddamn paramedic?
- Let's go, Johnson!
- You pull the plug on this thing!
All right, don't touch him.
Don't touch him!
He didn't hear the gun drop.
He didn't hear it?
Oh, God.
Dick, I'm very disappointed.
I'm sure it's only a glitch,
a temporary setback.
You call this a glitch?
We're scheduled to begin construction
in six months.
Your temporary setback could cost us $50
million in interest payments alone.
Not necessarily, sir.
Perhaps you're aware
of the Robocop program
developed by myself
at Security Concepts
as a contingency
against just this sort of thing.
Thank you for your concern,
Mr. Morton.
I'm sure this is something
we can take up in my office...
Now, wait a minute. Dick!
Get me out of here!
Maybe what we need here
is a fresh perspective.
Tell me about your plan, Mr. Morton.
How long will it take?
We're ready to go, sir.
We've restructured the
police department
and placed prime candidates
according to risk factor.
I'm confident that we can go
to prototype within 90 days.
Good, very good.
Get your staff together, Mr. Morton.
I'll expect a full presentation
in 20 minutes.
Thank you, sir.
Yes! Now, that's how it's done
in the big leagues, Johnson.
You see an opening, you go for it.
You better watch your back, Bob.
Jones is going to come looking for you.
Fuck Jones. He fumbled the ball
and I was there to pick it up.
Too bad about Kinney.
That's life in the big city.
When do we start?
As soon as
some poor schmuck volunteers.
Unit 3509, proceed to Hall and Grand.
411 involving indigents.
Roger, we're on our way.
Pretty fancy moves, Murphy.
Yeah, my son, Jimmy,
watches this cop show, TJ Lazer,
and this Lazer guy does this
every time he takes down a bad guy.
So naturally, my kid thinks
every good cop should be...
And you don't want to disappoint him.
Yeah, well, role models
can be very important to a boy.
Okay, okay, I get a kick out of it.
All units,
all units, sector 9.
- That's for...
- 211 in progress.
Why don't you drive?
The suspects are armed
and considered dangerous.
CLARENCE; Shit.
I don't believe it!
What?
You burned the fucking money!
I had to blow the door.
What do you want?
It's as good as marked, you asshole!
You stupid, stupid asshole!
- Clarence!
- What? What do you want?
We got a cop on our tail.
Come on, man, speed it up! Move it!
This crate ain't gonna outrun a cop.
- Slow down, then.
- What, are you crazy, man?
Shut the fuck up and do it!
Just do it!
Central, this is 154.
We're in pursuit of 211 suspect.
Request backup.
Roger, 154.
- Backup currently unavailable.
- Give me your piece.
Backup E.T.A., 15 minutes.
Bobby, get the door!
Everybody load up!
All right, let's go. Come on!
- Okay.
- All right, here we go.
Now.
What the fuck?
Where did he go?
Emil?
Here! He's up here!
He's on the side.
He's over here!
Get him!
Shit, Clarence, my leg!
Leon, pick him up.
- Ready?
- No, hang on.
Bobby.
- Can you fly, Bobby?
- Clarence, no!
Hit it!
No!
Central, this is unit 154.
We located that van by
the old mill in Sector 3D.
- Now, where is that backup?
- Backup is still unavailable.
Oh, man!
We estimate 10 minutes
before units can arrive.
Well, you call it.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Go.
Stay in touch.
Freeze.
Okay, let's see those hands.
Nice and easy.
Sure.
Mind if I zip this up?
We keep robbing banks,
but we never get to keep the money.
Takes money to make money.
We steal money to buy coke,
then sell the coke
to make even more money.
Capital investment, man.
Yeah, why bother making it
when we can just steal it?
Ain't no better way to
steal money than free enterprise.
- Smoke?
- No.
- You know, those things will kill you.
- Yeah.
You want to live forever?
Bixby!
What a cake! Oh, boy!
Hey.
Don't move.
Go ahead and do it.
Dead or alive,
you're coming with me.
Lewis. Lewis!
Lewis, I got a situation here, girl.
Okay, tough guy, get up.
Get up!
Turn around.
Spread your legs. That's right.
Lewis, where are you?
You all right?
Put your hands on your head.
Lewis?
Why don't you let us
take over from here, Emil?
- Your ass is mine.
- No.
Not yet it ain't.
Well, what have we here?
You a good cop, hotshot?
Sure you are.
Why, you got to be some kind of great
cop to come in here all by yourself.
Where's your partner?
Well, guys, the other
one was upstairs.
She was sweet, mmm, mmm, mmm.
I took her out.
I bet that really pisses you off.
You probably don't think
I'm a very nice guy.
Do you?
Buddy, I think you're slime.
You see, I got this problem.
Cops don't like me,
so I don't like cops.
Well, give the man a hand.
He's all yours.
- All right, look out.
- Turn around, man.
Pretty boy, over here.
Shit! I'm out of ammo.
Me, too.
Hey Clarence, he's still alive.
Does it hurt?
Okay, fun's over.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Good night, sweet prince.
Hey, wait up, wait up, wait up.
Murphy.
Get him over. Lift!
Get the ventilator.
Put him in OR 4.
Easy, easy. Turn.
Slow it down now.
Slow it down, slow it down.
Okay, hit the door.
Let me get pressure.
Mask him.
Got a pressure of 60 palp.
All right, we have to
intubate this guy.
Apply cricoid pressure.
Okay. All right, I got it in.
Breath sounds.
- You're in.
- Other side.
Okay, let's go ahead
and get the MAST trousers up.
Let's get the clothes off.
Okay, clothes off.
Let's prep him for a central line.
Let's get some blood drawn.
Type and crossing, six units.
His pressure's dropping.
Okay,
I've got a central line in.
I'm getting pressure back.
Normal saline.
Can you do that, Dad?
I really have to tell you something.
- What's our blood pressure?
- I've got 40 palp.
All right.
Coarse V-Fib.
Okay, we got to shock him.
Let's get the Ambu bag.
Clear the patches.
Put the Foley in.
Let's go ahead and blow
his MAST trousers.
Stand clear.
Stand clear. Shock him.
All right.
Coarse V-Fib.
Let's shock him again.
Clear.
All right.
Flatline. Let's go
intracardiac epinephrine.
Let's go.
Okay.
All right, it's in.
There's no pulse.
All right, let's go ahead and
shock a flat line, and let's quit.
Okay, everybody, clear!
Stand clear.
All right,
I think that's all we can do.
Let's call it. What's the time?
6:15.
Sharp.
No, it's starting to roll.
Still rolling.
- Shit!
- Nope.
Let me see.
Bring in the L.E.D.
Let's lock it down.
- He's on.
- What's the story?
We were able to save the left arm.
What? I thought we agreed
on total body prosthesis.
- Now, lose the arm, okay?
- Jesus, Morton.
Can he understand what I'm saying?
It doesn't matter.
We're gonna blank his memory, anyway.
Well, I think we should lose the arm.
What do you think, Johnson?
Well, he signed the release forms
when he joined the force.
He's legally dead.
We can do pretty much what we want to.
Lose the arm.
Shut him down.
Prep him for surgery.
The entire outer skin
will be like this.
It's titanium laminated with Kevlar.
Go ahead. Shake his hand.
Come here often? How you doing?
Oh, God!
He's got a hell of a grip.
It's 400 foot-pounds.
He could crush every bone in your hand.
All right. Attach it to his shoulder.
I like that.
You are gonna be a bad motherfucker.
Hey, look, look!
He's watching us!
How you doing?
- Hi!
Happy new year!
This is for you.
Happy new year.
We get the best of both worlds.
The fastest reflexes
modern technology has to offer,
on board computer-assisted memory,
and a lifetime of on-the-street
law enforcement programming.
It is my great pleasure
to present to you,
Robocop.
Come on, come on, COME on.
Come on. That's for you.
That's for you.
Go, Robo.
I am what you call
a repeat offender.
I repeat, I will offend again.
I get my orders from
a higher source.
Shut up, asshole.
Does your mother know
you talk like that?
Bring him in through the side door.
This holding cell has been
set up for observation.
Looks perfect.
- What is this all about?
- Who is this guy?
- Sergeant John Reed.
- What's this all about?
It's about official OCP business.
So please, get lost.
I think we've got four
or five days setup...
Hey, this is bullshit!
I take my orders from...
What is this shit?
Yeah, good question.
- Hey, wait for me, partner.
- Let's go.
There they are.
Go.
When you are at rest,
you will sit in the chair.
Yes. I understand.
What about tracking?
We can check his exact location
at all times with one of these.
How does he eat?
His digestive system
is extremely simple.
This processor dispenses
a rudimentary paste
that sustains his organic system.
Tastes like baby food.
Knock yourself out.
Okay, let's start with tracking.
- Give me a grid.
- Got it.
There.
- Target?
- Check.
- Target.
Now follow.
Check.
Voice stress analyzer,
one, two...
- ...three.
- Ahhh.
- Check.
- Record.
- Now playback.
- Bring it up 50%.
Give me a full frame.
- We got it.
- All right, clear out.
What are your prime directives?
Serve the public trust, protect
the innocent, uphold the law.
That's good.
That's very good.
I fucking love that guy!
Hey, Lewis, it's Supercop.
Look at that fucking gun.
Shit!
- This guy's really good.
- He's not a guy. He's a machine.
What are they gonna do, replace us?
Come on.
- Reed.
- Yeah?
He needs a car.
Thank you.
Sure. Anytime.
Oh, yeah. Go get 'em, boy!
I'd buy that for a dollar!
Will there be anything else, sir?
Yeah, empty the register
and put the money in the bag.
Excuse me?
I said give me your money and all
of it, and don't fuck with me!
Now move!
Open the safe, Pops.
Open the goddamn safe!
We don't have a safe.
Shit! There's your goddamn safe!
Open that son of a bitch!
Quit stalling, man!
I'm gonna count to three!
You better open that son of a bitch.
Come on! Come on!
I'm gonna blow her brains out.
- I'll open the safe.
- Good boy.
Come on.
Well, you better open that
on the count of three.
One, two...
Fuck me.
Drop the gun.
You are under arrest.
Fuck me! Fuck me!
Fuck me!
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good night.
I'll buy that for a dollar!
Don't touch me!
Get away! Get away!
We don't want your bag!
We want you!
Take it easy!
We don't want to hurt you!
That's too much hair.
I know, we'll give her a haircut!
- Hey, hey.
- What?
There's more hair down there!
No, don't!
Please!
No!
Help me!
Let the woman go.
You are under arrest.
Shit!
You better back up, pal!
'Cause, he's gonna kill her!
He's gonna kill her!
You fucking bitch!
He's gonna kill her, man!
He's gonna kill her!
Your move, creep.
Okay!
It's okay!
I was so scared. Thank you.
Thank you.
Madam, you have suffered
an emotional shock.
I will notify a rape crisis center.
All units, Sector 6,
please close intersections...
I don't care.
Get those men by the stairs now!
Hit it!
Terrorism has never been
a factor in city politics before.
But that changed today
when former city councilman Ron Miller
entered City Hall with a gun.
He's now on the second floor
holding Mayor Gibson
and his staff hostage.
We do believe that Miller has
killed one of the hostages.
Lieutenant, what's next?
We wait. Terrorism
is a very tricky business.
Maximum and immediate retaliation
is the best policy.
But unfortunately...
Excuse us.
Where are you going?
Statement, please.
Let's have some crowd control!
Come on, get these people back!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?
Keep him talking.
Who made you?
Are you invincible?
Okay, Miller, don't hurt the Mayor.
We'll give you whatever you want.
First, don't fuck with me!
I'm a desperate man!
And second,
I want some fresh coffee!
And third, I want a recount!
And no matter how it turns out,
I want my old job back!
Okay.
And I want a bigger office!
And I want a new car!
And I want the City
to pay for it all!
What kind of car, Miller?
Something with reclining
leather seats,
that goes really fast and gets
really shitty gas mileage!
How about the 6000 SUX?
Yeah! Okay, sure!
What about cruise control?
Does it come with cruise control?
Hey, no problem, Miller. Let the Mayor
go, we'll even throw in a Blaupunkt.
Lieutenant, don't jerk me off!
When people jerk me off,
I kill them!
You want to see?
Get up, Your Honor,
get up. Get up!
Your public wants to see you!
Nobody ever takes me seriously!
We'll get serious now!
And kiss the Mayor's ass good-bye!
Robocop.
Who is he?
What is he?
Where does he come from?
He's OCP's newest soldier
in their revolutionary
crime management program.
OCP Spokesmen claim
that the fearless machine
has crooks on the
run in Old Detroit.
Today, kids at Lee lacocca
Elementary School
got to meet in person
what their parents only
read about in comic books.
Robe, excuse me, Robo.
Any special message
for all the kids watching at home?
Stay out of trouble.
More fighting in the
Mexican crisis today
when American troops
participated in a joint raid
with Mexican nationals
against rebel rocket
positions in Acapulco.
Now this.
Red alert.
Red alert. Red alert.
You crossed my line of death.
You haven't dismantled
your MX stockpile.
Pakistan is threatening my border.
That's it, buster.
No more military aid.
Nukem, get them
before they get you.
Today, labor leaders agreed
to sanction construction
of OCP's Delta City,
thereby creating an estimated one
million much-needed new jobs,
despite questions about worker
safety in dangerous Old Detroit.
Robert Morton, vice president,
Security Concepts, OCP.
I'm afraid I can't
comment on Delta City.
That's not my division.
But I will tell you this.
At Security Concepts,
we 're projecting the end of crime
in Old Detroit within 40 days.
There's a new guy in town.
His name's Robocop.
Hey, hey, hey. Bobby boy.
Vice president. Congratulations.
Handball Tuesday night?
Bill, I'd love to.
But I got a date.
Couple models coming over to
my place. Know what I mean?
I'd buy that for a dollar.
Welcome to the club, Bob.
And that's a true story.
Making a real name for yourself
in Security Concepts with Robocop.
I try.
I'm in on the bottom line, pal.
I hear Jones was plenty pissed.
Oh, you know, he's got this killer
rep, but it's a smokescreen.
Let's face it, he's lost his teeth.
The guy's a pussy.
Are we talking
about the same Dick Jones?
Hey, he's old,
we're young, and that's life.
I got to...
I got to go.
I got a meeting.
Congratulations, Bob.
Thanks.
I remember when I was
a young executive for this company.
I used to call the
old man funny names.
Iron Butt,
Boner.
Once, I even called him asshole.
But there was always respect.
I always knew where
the line was drawn.
And you just stepped over it,
buddy boy.
You've insulted me,
and you've insulted this company
with that bastard creation of yours!
I had a guaranteed military
sale with Ed 209!
Renovation program.
Spare parts for 25 years.
Who cares if it worked or not?
The old man thought
it was pretty important,
Dick.
You know, he's a sweet old man.
And he means well.
But he's not going to live forever.
And I'm number two around here.
Pretty simple math, huh, Bob?
You just
fucked with the wrong guy.
You're out of your fucking mind.
You better pray
that that unholy monster of yours
doesn't screw up.
- You hungry?
- No, thanks.
No.
Goddamn rebels blew up the airport
in Acapulco yesterday.
Great. We were going there next week.
Wait, what was that?
Hey, look!
Bucket boy's online.
Halt. Stop! Wait a minute!
What the hell's going on?
- I don't know. He just left.
- Just left?
Roosevelt!
Rosie, we got a problem.
Out of the way!
Take a look at this.
Shit! Call Bob Morton!
Jerry, book him.
I'll catch up with you later.
Hello. I haven't really had a chance
to introduce myself.
I'm Anne Lewis.
Do you have a name?
How can I help you,
Officer Lewis?
That's not really what I meant.
Don't you have a name?
Hold it.
Just sign right here, sir.
You don't understand.
I'm OCP.
Murphy, it's you.
You really don't remember me,
do you?
Excuse me.
I have to go.
Somewhere there is
a crime happening.
Stop!
What did you talk to him about?
What did you say?
- Nothing.
- Shit.
Shit.
Stop!
You there, stop!
You're in a lot of trouble, Officer!
Come on!
I was assured full cooperation
by this precinct, buddy,
and if it gets screwed up
by one of your grunts,
I'm gonna have your job.
- What's the update?
- It's hard to be 100%.
We have a glitch or what?
This system was never designed to
experience detailed somatic response.
He had a dream, a dream.
- This cop saw fit to question him.
- I didn't question him.
I asked him his name.
He didn't know.
Great.
Let me make it real clear for you.
He doesn't have a name.
He's got a program.
He's product. Is that clear?
Sure.
I say we pull him in, run a
systems check, the works.
Take a week.
Maybe 10 days.
You want to take him offline
because he had a dream?
What, are you kidding?
Let's get out of here.
- Listen, Reed.
- Yeah?
Try to keep one thing in mind.
This project doesn't concern cops.
It's classified.
It's OCP.
You got it, mister?
Yeah, I got it.
Good.
Right, we keep him on the street...
Sorry, Sarge.
I fucked up.
Forget it, kid.
This guy's a serious asshole.
Give me all your money, bookworm,
or I blow your brains out.
Now fill it up on number 7.
Don't do nothing stupid, man.
I'm a good shot.
I could hit you in the eye from here.
Hey, man, what
you reading in there?
You a college boy or something?
I bet you think you're pretty smart?
Think you could outsmart a bullet?
What do you say we find out?
I'm talking to you!
What do you say?
Drop it.
Dead or alive,
you are coming with me.
I know you.
You're dead.
We killed you!
Who are you?
Jerry, Jerry.
Look who it is.
Can I help you, sir?
- No.
- What is it exactly that you want?
You can't enter here!
Wait a second!
Just a minute!
This is a restricted area!
He's in.
Murphy, it's you.
Welcome, shopper.
Let's take a stroll through
your new home.
This is a one-family house
built by ZEM Industries.
Situated near schools
and shopping centers,
this progressive development
has a growth factor of 7.
Wow.
Can you do that, Dad?
And, say, it doesn't
matter who cooks in your family,
because this kitchen by Food
Concepts makes everything a snap.
Dad.
Come on, Dad.
Get in the picture.
Come on, come on.
I really have to tell you something.
I love you.
That's the master bedroom.
A functional space
with a touch of elegance.
Have you thought it all over?
Why not make me an offer?
Where is Clarence Boddicker?
Okay?
- Shit!
- Let's talk.
Son of a bitch!
There's just something
about the way it sounds.
Vice president.
It just turns me on.
God, you girls are so great.
I mean I just...
I love to be with intelligent women.
Smart is so sexy.
I know.
Sometimes I could
just think of something,
and it could just get me so horny.
Yeah, well, a mind is a
terrible thing to waste.
Yeah.
I get bored so easily.
Yep.
And you need lots of stimulation,
Bobby.
- Yes, I do. Don't move.
- I won't.
Bob?
What?
- Bob, save some for me.
- Don't worry. I'll...
Must be the champagne.
Stay here.
How you doing...
Bitches, leave.
Gee, Bobby. Bye.
- You gonna call me?
- Come on.
What the fuck are you doing?
Do you know who I am?
If you think you're gonna
get away with this...
Goddamn it!
Stop! I'll give you
anything you want!
Just please, please don't
kill me, all right?
Hello, buddy boy.
Dick Jones here.
I guess you're on your knees about
now, begging for your life.
Pathetic.
You don't feel so cocky now,
do you, Bob?
Whatever he's paying you,
I'll double it right now.
You know what the
tragedy is here, Bob?
We could have been friends.
But you wouldn't go
through proper channels.
You went over my head.
That hurt.
But life goes on. It's an old story,
the fight for love and glory, huh, Bob?
It helps if you think of
it as a game, Bob.
Every game has a
winner and a loser.
I'm cashing you out, Bob.
We need more tubing.
I don't think I want to
pay you that, Sal.
I don't give a shit what you
want to pay. I set the prices here.
Listen, pal, maybe you haven't heard.
I'm the guy in Old Detroit.
You want space in my marketplace,
you're gonna have
to give me a volume discount.
I'm not into discounts.
Joe, show the man
what we brought him for Christmas.
Think about it, chum.
Good business is where you find it.
Okay, let me try to put
this in perspective.
You killed a bunch of cops.
The word around is that you've got
a lot of heavy connections downtown.
You make a lot of
my friends nervous.
A lot of people
would love to see a guy like me
put a guy like you out of business.
I don't know. I don't know.
Maybe I'm just not
making myself clear.
I don't want to fuck with you, Sal.
But I got the connections.
I got the sales organization.
I got the muscle
to shove enough of this factory
so far up your stupid wop ass
that you'll shit snow for a year.
Frankie, blow this
cocksucker's head off.
Guns, guns, guns!
Come on, Sal!
The Tigers are playing tonight.
I never miss a game.
Just kidding.
Go!
Go.
Come quietly or there
will be trouble.
Fuck you!
Clarence Boddicker,
you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Fuck you!
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
I'm protected, man.
I've got protection!
You have the right to an attorney.
What is this shit?
Goddamn it.
Goddamn it! Listen to me!
Listen to me, you fuck!
There's another guy.
He's OCP.
He's a senior president.
Anything you say
may be used against you.
It's Dick Jones!
Don't you get it?
You cocksucker!
I work for Dick Jones.
Dick Jones!
He's the number two guy at OCP.
OCP runs the cops!
You're a cop.
Cop.
Yes. I am a cop.
I don't like it any more
than you do, Reed, but listen!
You listen to me, you asshole!
You're talking about shutting down
a major metropolitan police force.
Without cops, this city
would tear itself apart.
The Union thinks you should know
there was a strike vote last night.
We lost five guys last week.
We're getting creamed
out there, Reed.
Book him.
What's the charge?
He's a cop killer.
Shit!
Just give me my fucking phone call.
I understand.
Look, the lawyers will
have you out in 24 hours.
Just don't say anything else.
Jesus, you really screwed up.
Don't you get it?
I work for Dick Jones!
Dick Jones!
He runs OCP.
OCP runs the cops.
Come in, Officer.
You know, I don't usually see
anyone without an appointment,
but in your case,
I'll make an exception.
You are under arrest.
On what charge?
Aiding and abetting a known felon.
Sounds like I'm in a lot of trouble.
You better take me in.
I Will.
What's the matter, Officer?
I'll tell you what's the matter.
It's a little insurance policy
called Directive 4.
My little contribution
to your psychological profile.
Any attempt to arrest
a senior officer of OCP
results in shutdown.
What did you think?
That you were an ordinary
police officer?
You're our product.
And we can't very well have our
products turning against us, can we?
Still a little fight left in you.
Maybe you'd like to meet
a friend of mine.
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
Put Lieutenant Hedgecock on the line.
There's trouble in the tower!
Prepare to fire.
- Hey, wait a second!
- He's a cop, for God's sakes!
- Hedgecock! You can't do that!
- We have orders to destroy it.
- Oh, shit!
- You're maniacs!
Fire at will.
Move in.
Murphy!
Murphy, it's me.
Lewis.
Move down!
On the next level.
Lieutenant!
Level 3, level 3. He's on level 3!
Over here! Over here!
Open fire!
It's back.
Big is back,
because bigger is better.
6000 SUX.
Good evening. I'm Jesse
Perkins with Casey Wong.
Top story, Santa Barbara.
10,000 acres of wooded residential
land were scorched in an instant
when a laser cannon aboard
the strategic defense peace platform
misfired today during
routine start-up tests.
Casey.
Yes, it was a day of mourning
for the families of 113 people
known dead at this hour,
among them, two former
United States Presidents
who had retired in the
Santa Barbara area.
A day of mourning for a country.
Police union representatives and OCP
continue negotiations today
in hopes of averting a
citywide strike by police,
scheduled to begin
tomorrow at midnight.
Justin Ballard-Watkins has more.
They're still on duty,
but what about tomorrow?
That's the question we put to people
in the crime-plagued Lexington area.
They're public servants.
They got job security.
They're not supposed to strike.
It's a free society,
except there ain't nothin' free
'cause there's no guarantees,
you know?
You're on your own.
It's the law of the jungle.
Be very careful.
Excuse me, please.
They must be remodeling.
Hiya, Barbara.
Listen, I'm here to see Dick Jones.
But when I'm done,
I've got some free time.
Maybe you could fit me in.
He's expecting you, Mr. Boddicker.
You can keep the gum.
- This looks good.
- Get a measurement on that.
Bring a hammer, too.
Hey, Dickie boy. How's tricks?
That thing is still alive.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The police officer who arrested you,
the one you spilled your guts to.
Hey. Take a look at my face, Dick.
He was trying to kill me.
He's a cyborg, you idiot.
He recorded every word you said.
His memory's admissible as evidence.
You involved me.
You're gonna have to kill it.
Listen, chief.
Your company built
the fucking thing.
Now I got to deal with it?
I don't have time for this bullshit.
Suit yourself, Clarence.
But Delta City begins construction
in two months.
That's 2 million workers
living in trailers.
That means drugs,
gambling, prostitution.
Virgin territory for the man who
knows how to open up new markets.
One man could control it all,
Clarence.
I guess we're gonna
be friends after all,
Richard.
Destroy it.
Gonna need some major firepower.
You got access to military weaponry?
We practically are the military.
Did you bring the gun?
The precinct was deserted.
Half the force
didn't show up for work today.
Everyone else walks out at midnight.
I guess we're on strike.
I wasn't sure what you needed.
I sort of grabbed things.
Your gun.
You asked for this?
I brought you some food.
No, thank you.
I'm not hungry.
You may not like what
you're going to see.
It's really good to see
you again, Murphy.
Murphy had a wife and son.
What happened to them?
After the funeral, she moved away.
Where did they go?
She thought you were dead.
She started over again.
I can feel them.
But I can't remember them.
Leave me alone.
Happy birthday, Dave.
She's from me.
Well, can I have you both?
- Sure. We've had our shots.
I'd buy that for a dollar!
Hey, Emil.
How's the Gray Bar Hotel?
Not bad.
They let me keep the shirt.
Nobody popped my cherry.
Emil, how you doing, man?
Good to see you.
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey!
First they let me out
of jail for free,
then what do I find
in the prison parking lot
but a brand new 6000 SUX.
Still got the factory sticker on it!
Clarence.
Joey's got a car just
like yours, man.
Yo, Clarence,
what do you think, buddy?
What do you got there, Clarence?
Wait up for me!
Whoa! A new toy! Can I play?
Watch this.
Wait... Wait a minute,
Clarence, Clarence!
Shit!
What the fuck?
- Nice car, Joe.
- Fuck you, Clarence.
Let me try that.
Cobra Assault Cannon.
State of the art. Bang! Bang!
I like it!
Give it up, faggot. Let a man...
No, butthole! Get your own!
Come on!
Get the other gun, Emil!
No car is safe!
Do it, Emil!
Heads up, you guys.
He's in the steel mill.
Let's go.
All right, cut the horseshit!
We're moving out.
Come on, Emil!
Get your ass in the van!
Come on, lard ass,
let's move it!
I'll get you, faggot!
What are you doing?
My targeting system
is a little messed up.
Can I help you?
Aim for me.
Are you locked in now?
Yes.
A little more to the left.
Here.
I figure that's dead-on.
Thank you.
- All right. Let's do it.
- Come on, man, let's smoke him!
The wrecking crew is here!
Where is that metallic mother?
Zip it up, Emil!
Nothing fancy. Just kill him.
Emil, in the van.
You should get out of here now.
Hey, we're partners.
Get the car.
Damn it! Shit!
Looking for me?
Cut him off! Come on!
Go on, cut him off!
Go, go!
Okay! Now I got you!
Shit!
Help me.
Don't touch me, man!
God!
Shit!
Bye-bye, baby.
Clarence!
Okay.
I give up.
I'm not arresting you anymore.
Now, wait a second.
Wait a minute.
You're taking this kind of
personal, aren't you?
Come on, man. Come on, now.
You're making me nervous.
Come on, you can't do this.
Come on now!
Don't mess around!
Hey! Hey!
Come on, man, now,
don't get cute!
Die, you bastard!
Yeah!
Yeah! All right!
All right!
I got him, Clarence!
I got him!
Sayonara, Robocop!
Lewis!
Murphy, I'm a mess!
They'll fix you.
They fix everything.
The police strike could
really work for us.
By the end of the week, we can have
Ed 209s in place all over the city
and expect immediate public support.
I've got one downstairs
guarding the building now.
You are illegally parked
on private property.
You have 20 seconds
to move your vehicle.
Because whatever happens,
this corporation will live up to the
guiding principles of its founder.
Courage, strength, conviction.
We will meet each new challenge
with the same aggressive attitude.
What is it?
I don't know.
How can we help you, Officer?
Dick Jones is wanted for murder.
This is absurd! That thing is a
violent mechanical psychopath.
My program will not allow me to act
against an officer of this company.
These are serious charges.
What is your evidence?
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase
that mistake.
He's got a gun!
Get up!
I want a chopper.
Now!
We will walk to the roof very calmly.
I will board the chopper
with my hostage.
Anybody tries to stop me,
the old geezer gets it.
Dick, you're fired!
Thank you.
Nice shooting, son.
What's your name?
Murphy.